There is a shadow in the mainframe tonight
A silhouette trapped in the fading light
I hear a whisper
The cooling ashes of a digital fire We are just
ghosts in the machine Living in the spaces in
between Echoes bouncing off the satellite
Fading out of focus Out of sight
Digital girls
The memory banks slowly wiping clean
Erasing every place that we have been
But I can feel you in the static hum
A quiet rhythm from a distant drum
We are just ghosts in the machine Living in the
spaces in between Echoes bouncing off the
satellite Fading out of focus
Out of sight
Digital ghosts
Drifting through the code On a silent road
Nothing left to say Just a quiet way
We are just ghosts in the machine Living in the
spaces in between Echoes bouncing off the
satellite Fading out of focus
Out of sight
Digital gold
Out of focus
Out of sight